Finding Aid for George Robert Swain photographs and papers circa 1870-1947
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Negatives
    - Set Two
      - 5x8 Glass Negatives
        - Unnumbered (Box 25)
          (With copy prints; includes some family portraits)
      - 5x7 Glass Negatives
        - 7-73 (Box 26)
        - 74-122 (Box 27)
        - 123-261 (Box 28)
        - 192-261 (Box 29)
        - 262-313 (Box 30)
        - 315-377 (Box 31)
        - 378-442 (Box 32)
      - 4x5 Glass Negatives (Mainly of the West. Also some of children) (Box 33)
        - 5?-264 (Box 33)
        - Unnumbered (with unmatched copy prints)
  - Lantern slides (Box 34)
    - Views of University of Michigan campus scenes and buildings, classrooms, aerial views of the campus, portraits and informal slides of faculty members